BRAC Chicago Files 5488 A
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Letter of Instructions, 1952 (Box 27, Folder 25)
- Notice to Management Non-Compliance (Box 27, Folder 26)
- Letters to General Chairmen, Non-Members - Union Shop (Box 27, Folder 27)
- Letters to be sent by Local Chairmen (Box 27, Folder 28)
- Forms A-B-C Notice to Carrier of Failure to Comply Us Subsequent, 1957 (Box 27, Folder 29)
  1/1/1957
- Form B - Atlantic Coast Line for Use Roads Having ACL Memo to US Rule (Box 27, Folder 30)
- 40 Hour Week - General, 1949-1969 (Box 27, Folder 31)
- Interpretation 6/24/68 Agreement (Rest Days), 1968 (Box 27, Folder 32)
- Chesapeake and Ohio Agreement - Requiring Train Dispatchers to Observe Rest Days before returning to our branch of service, 1960 (Box 27, Folder 33)
- Hour Week Agreement, 1949 (Box 27, Folder 34)
  March 19,1949
- MISSING BOX (Box 28)
- Decisions and Supplements Forty Hour Week Agreement, 1949-1958 (Box 29, Folder 1)
- Forty Hour Week Committee - General, 1949-1962 (Box 29, Folder 2)
- Unsettled disputes before the 40 Hour Week Committee, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 3)
- 40 Hour Week - Monthly Rated Positions, 1952-1968 (Box 29, Folder 4)
- 40 Hour Week - Free Tranportation - Relief Employees, 1948-1955 (Box 29, Folder 5)
- 40 Hour Week - Arbitration Awards, 1956 (Box 29, Folder 6)
- Department of Tranportation - General Correpondence, 1968-1972 (Box 29, Folder 7)
- Interstate Commerce Commission - General Correpondence, 1965-1972 (Box 29, Folder 8)
- Interstate Commerce Commission Act and Amendments, 1922-1967 (Box 29, Folder 9)
- Interstate Commerce Commission - Personnel, 1961-1966 (Box 29, Folder 10)
- Interstate Commerce Commission Bureau of Safety, Locamotive, Inspection and Service - Safety - General Correspondence, 1957- 1972 (Box 29, Folder 11)
- Safety Highway - Railroad Grade Crossings, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 12)
- Interstate Commerce Commission Accident Reports, 1960-1971 (Box 29, Folder 13)
- Ex Parte 72 (Interstate Commerce Commission Regulation designating classes of Employees as Subordinate Officials), 1920-1965 (Box 29, Folder 14)
- Interstate Commerce Commission Order - Ex Parte No. 73, 1959 (Box 29, Folder 15)
- Ex Parte 131, 1964-1968 (Box 29, Folder 16)
- Ex Parte 174 (Box 30, Folder 1)
- Ex Parte 179 (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Ex Parte 217, 1961 (Box 30, Folder 3)
- Ex Parte 230, 1966 (Box 30, Folder 4)
- Ex Parte 243, 1965-1968 (Box 30, Folder 5)
- Ex Parte 246, 1965-1969 (Box 30, Folder 6)
- Interstate Commerce Commission Dockets - General, 1958-1969 (Box 30, Folder 7)
- Adequacies Passenger Service - Various Docket Numbers, 1966-1969 (Box 30, Folder 8)
- Docket 13413 - Automatic Train Control Device, 1965-1968 (Box 30, Folder 9)
- Docket 13528 - Power Brakes, 1967-1969 (Box 30, Folder 10)
- Docket 32406 - Air Brakes, 1966-1968 (Box 30, Folder 11)
- Interstate Commerce Commission Reporting divisions, 1955-1968 (Box 30, Folder 12)
- Legal Expenses a/c Various Interstate Commerce Commission and BA-AP Dockets, 1963-1964 (Box 30, Folder 13)
- Board of Transport Commissioners - Canada, 1958-1966 (Box 30, Folder 14)
- Board of Transport Commissioners - Railway Association of Canada Operating Rules and Interpretations, 1954-1965 (Box 30, Folder 15)
- Interstate Commerce Commission Line Abandonments and Train Discontinuancies - General Correspondence, 1949-1968 (Box 30, Folder 16)
- Improvement in Passenger Service - General Correspondence, 1949-1968 (Box 30, Folder 17)
- Commuter Problems - General, 1960-1967 (Box 30, Folder 18)
- Protective Conditions - General Correspondence, 1962-1966 (Box 30, Folder 19)
- ACL-L&N Conditions (Modifications of WJP Agreement), 1959 (Box 31, Folder 1)
- Burlington Agreement, 1944-1969 (Box 31, Folder 2)
- Precedent Setting Awards - Extra Employees Subject to Burlington Conditions Nos. 41-42-43-44 SBA 226 Mkt, 1962 (Box 31, Folder 3)
- Chicago and North Western Conditions - Docket 15250 (Box 31, Folder 4)
- Protective Agreement in event of Merger Chicago and North Western and Chicago Great Western, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 5)
- C&O and B&O Protective Conditions (Box 31, Folder 6)
- Protective Agreement in event of Merger Great Northern Pacific and Burlington Lines, 1966 (Box 31, Folder 7)
- New Orleans Union Pass Terminal conditions (Docket 15920), 1936-1962 (Box 31, Folder 8)
- Norfolk and Western and Virginian Conditions, 1959 (Box 31, Folder 9)
- Norfolk and Western Railway Implementing Agreement for Protection Employees a/c Agreement Merger Nickel Plate - Wabash - P&WV - FDS 21510-14, 1962-1964 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  1/10/1962
- Oklahoma Conditions, 1944-1963 (Box 31, Folder 11)
- Penn and Central Protective Conditions and Implementing Agreement, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  4/6/1968
- Southern-Central of GA. Protective - Protective Conditions, 1962-1966 (Box 31, Folder 13)
- Protective Agreement in event of Merger Union Pacific Railraod and CRI&P (Box 31, Folder 14)
- IC-GM&O Merger F.D. 25103-4-5-6, 1970-1971 (Box 31, Folder 15)
- C&NW - Milwaukee Merger F.D. 24182-3-4, 1966-1971 (Box 31, Folder 16)
- MERGER - C&NW-UP-CRI&P-SP-AT&SF SPTransportation Company FDS 22688-9, 23285-6-7, 235956, 23919-20, MC-F-9222, 1962-1969 (Box 31, Folder 17)
- Chicago Great Western and Sooline FD 23388 and 23389 (Box 32, Folder 1)
- Merger - Chicago and North Western, 1964-1968 (Box 32, Folder 1)
- UP-SP-Rock Island Merger, 1968 (Box 32, Folder 2)
- Monon - L&N Merger F.D. 25309, 1970-1971 (Box 32, Folder 3)
- IC - Mississippi Central Merger F.D. 24024, 1963-1967 (Box 32, Folder 4)
- Tennessee Central Susp. Operators F.D. 24964, 25163, 25032. 35183, 24161, 25279, 25274, 1968-1969 (Box 32, Folder 5)
- C&O - B&O Merger - Western Md. F.D. 23178, 1971 (Box 32, Folder 6)
- Norfolk and Western - C&O Merger F.Dockets 23832 and 23833, 1965-1971 (Box 32, Folder 7)
- N&W - C&O - B&O Merger, 1969-1970 (Box 32, Folder 8)
- Penn Central Merger F.D. 21989 Other Organizations - Implementing Agreements, 1968-1971 (Box 32, Folder 9)
- Penn-Central Papers ARL, Negotiations, 1964-1966 (Box 33, Folder 1)
- Pennsylvania-New York Central Fi. Docket 21989 Merger DANYC, 1968-1969 (Box 33, Folder 2)
- File 2 - Pennsylvania-New York Central Merger Fi. Docket 21989, 1968-1969 (Box 33, Folder 3)
- NYNH&H F.D. 21669-12131-21808-9, 1956-1969 (Box 33, Folder 4)
- L&N - C&EI F.D. 25309-10, 1968-1971 (Box 33, Folder 5)
- StLSW-MP-Alton and Southern F.D. 23935-24075, 1966-1969 (Box 34, Folder 1)
- T&P - KO&G - MV - OCAA AT&SF-OCAA F.D. 22274-5 22382, 1963-1964 (Box 34, Folder 2)
- Seaboard Airline - AEL, Coast Line Fi. Docket 21215 - Merger, 1957-1968 (Box 34, Folder 3)
- Seaboard Airline - AEL, Coast Line Fi. Docket 21215 - Merger, 1957-1968 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  file 2
- Erie- Lackawanna Merger (Docket 20707), 1961-1962 (Box 34, Folder 5)
- Erie - Lackawanna Merger (Docket 20707) File 2, 1960-1962 (Box 35, Folder 1)
- Erie - Lackawanna - Docket 20707 Merger Claims, 1962-1965 (Box 35, Folder 2)
- Erie - Lackawanna Merger (Docket 20707) Newspaper Clippings and Maps, 1962-1964 (Box 35, Folder 3)
- Baltimore and Ohio - Chesapeake and Ohio F.D. 21160-21161 Merger, 1961-1965 (Box 35, Folder 4)
- CB&Q - NP - GN - SP&S Merger F.D. Numbers 21478-21479-21480 (Box 36, Folder 1)
- Great Northern Pacific and Burlington Lines Merger - Protective Conditions, Organizations Concerned F.D. 21478-9-80 (KST Minn. Docket A-7958) (Box 36, Folder 2)
- CB&Q - NP - GN - SP&S Merger F.D. Numbers 21478-21479-21480 (Box 36, Folder 3)
- CB&Q - NP - GN - SP&S Merger F.D. Numbers 21478-21479-21480 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  file 3
- Southern Railway F.D. 21400, 1962-1969 (Box 37, Folder 1)
- Florida East Coast Re: C.W. McCoy and E.H. Taylor Dismissal Claim, 1962-1963 (Box 37, Folder 2)
- Claim - Discipline, H. Pitman Houston Belt and Terminal Company, 1957 (Box 37, Folder 3)
- Claim - Violation Rule 2(a) and (b) Red Caps at 125th St. Station New York Central Railroad, 1958-1961 (Box 37, Folder 4)
- Howard, Francis L. Claim - Discipline Case Pennsylvania Railroad Company, 1956-1960 (Box 37, Folder 5)
- Claim - Overtime Pay, Violation of Article 15(g), George Phillips Chicago and Western Ind. Railraod Company, 1957-1958 (Box 37, Folder 6)
- Improper Abolishment of Job Pullman Laundry - St. Louis Pullman Company, 1946-1956 (Box 37, Folder 7)
- Gardner, WM.J. - Discipline Case Northern Pacific Terminal Company, 1955 (Box 37, Folder 8)
- Improper Application of Paragraph D, and Rule 13(b) Southern Pacific, 1937-1955 (Box 37, Folder 9)
- New Orleans Union Passenger Terminal - Claim: Discipline, Warren Glass, 1960-1961 (Box 37, Folder 10)
- Time Claim - Rule Violation - Southern PAcific Catherill, et al., 1956-1961 (Box 37, Folder 11)
- Southern Pacific Company Claim: Violation of Scope Rule Red Cap Dillard, 1961-1965 (Box 37, Folder 12)
- Claim: General Grievance Covering Hospitalization Savannah Union Station Company, 1957-1958 (Box 37, Folder 13)
- Savannah Union Terminal Claim, 1960-1962 (Box 37, Folder 14)
- Violation of Rule 2 Seniority - Southern Pacific Company J.Hunt, 1956-1963 (Box 37, Folder 15)
- Southern Railway Re: T.M.Borders Discipline, 1961-1963 (Box 37, Folder 16)
- Savannah Union Station Company - Violation of Scope Rule, 1960-1964 (Box 37, Folder 17)
- Claim - Zack Storey New York Central Railroad, 1953-1955 (Box 37, Folder 18)
- Bridges, Julius - Discipline, Discharge ALLIED Local 298, 1966-1967 (Box 37, Folder 19)
- Meal Period - Southern Pacific Claim, 1953-1955 (Box 38, Folder 1)
- Pennsylvannia Railroad - Discipline Case Re: M.C. Brown, 1958-1961 (Box 38, Folder 2)
- Clark, Freeman Discipline Case New Orleans Union Passenger Terminal, 1956 (Box 38, Folder 3)
- Mishandling of Baggage Rule Violation Cincinnati Union Terminal Company, 1956 (Box 38, Folder 4)
- Claim: A.W. Ross Illinois Central - Violation of Contract (Box 38, Folder 5)
- Walker, Charles Southern Railway System Ezhibits, 1954-1956 (Box 38, Folder 6)
- Award #9041 - Robert Freeman vs. Southern Railroad System, 1955-1960 (Box 38, Folder 7)
- Harding, J.C., Train Porter Southern Railway Job Abolishment, 1950-1965 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  Southern Railway Grievance - Abolishment of Job
- Walker, Willie Mae Claim: Savannah Union Station Company Violation of Agreement, 1957 (Box 38, Folder 9)
- Savannah Union Station Company - Violation of Rules, 1956 (Box 38, Folder 10)
- Deal, W.B. Grievance Re: Dismissal, Coordination Allow/Savannah Union Station Local 220, 1962 (Box 38, Folder 11)
- Savannah Union Station Company - Abandonment of Facilities Local 220, 1962 (Box 38, Folder 12)
- Claim: Rule Violations - Southern Pacific Company, 1956-1961 (Box 38, Folder 13)
- Wertherman Bag Case, 1957-1961 (Box 38, Folder 14)
- Washington Terminal Company Ellison L. Robbs, 1960-1964 (Box 38, Folder 15)
- Walker, Charles, waiter Discipline Case Southern Railway System, 1954-1955 (Box 38, Folder 16)
- Sample Section 6 Notices for Rate Adjustments under WJPA Coordinations - Sample Preambles for Implementing Agreements (Box 38, Folder 17)
- Washington Job Protection Agreement - Interpretations and Instructions, 1960-1966 (Box 38, Folder 18)
- Washington Job Protection Agreement and Amendments, 1936-1968 (Box 38, Folder 19)
- Washington Job Protection Agreement - Applications to become Parties to, 1939-1968 (Box 38, Folder 20)
- Supplemental Pension Plan - General (In Division Order), 1960-1971 (Box 38, Folder 21)
- Supplemental Pension Plans - General, 1959-1966 (Box 38, Folder 22)
- Supplemental Pension Plan - Grand Division Officers - ORT (President - Vice Presidents and Designated Officers), 1969 (Box 38, Folder 23)
- Supplemental Pension Plan - ORT Subordinate Division Officers, 1956-1966 (Box 38, Folder 24)
- US Steel Pension Plan - Cy of Plan - General Correspondence, 1960-1966 (Box 39, Folder 1)
- Bessemer and Lake Erie Railroad Company - Supplemental Pension Plan, 1957-1970 (Box 39, Folder 2)
- Elgin, Joliet, and Eastern - Supplemental Pension Plan, 1960-1969 (Box 39, Folder 3)
- Duluth, Missabe and Iron Range - Supplemental Pension, 1957-1967 (Box 39, Folder 4)
- Civil Service - Retirement and Disability, 1953-1957 (Box 39, Folder 5)
- Railraod Retirement Act 1935 and Subsequent Changes, 1970-1972 (Box 39, Folder 6)
- Amendment - Railroad Retirement Act HR-13300 - Funds to pay Supplemental Annuities, 1968-1971 (Box 39, Folder 7)
- Presidential Commission on Reorganization Railroad Retirement Act, 1971 (Box 39, Folder 8)
- Compulsory Retirement - General, 1959-1971 (Box 40, Folder 1)
- Sample Compulsory Retirement Letters and Extra Copies of Signed Agreements (Box 40, Folder 2)
- Railraod Unemployment Insurance Act - Copies, 1946-1955 (Box 40, Folder 3)
- Statistics - General Correspondence, 1956-1965 (Box 40, Folder 4)
- Bureau of Labor Statistics, 1951-1965 (Box 40, Folder 5)
- Railway Labor Act - General Correspondence - Proposed Amendments, 1960-1970 (Box 40, Folder 6)
- Railway Labor Act - Copies of Amendments to, 1934-1972 (Box 40, Folder 7)
- Railway Labor Board Data, 1919-1941 (Box 40, Folder 8)
- Railway Labor Act: Procedures - Application Interpretation, 1931-1964 (Box 40, Folder 9)
- Power of Attorney Forms, 1936-1955 (Box 40, Folder 10)
- Samples of Section 6 Notices - Sample Agreements, Sample Strike Ballots, 1954-1970 (Box 40, Folder 11)
- Section 6 Notices - Railway Labor Act - General, 1959-1966 (Box 40, Folder 12)
- Non-Application NRAB Awards: General - Chamberlain Committee, 1937-1951 (Box 40, Folder 13)
- Non-Application NRAB Awards: Division Order=Chamberlain Committee, 1961-1968 (Box 40, Folder 14)
- Non-Application NRAB Awards: Other Organizations=Chamberlain Committee, 1962-1968 (Box 40, Folder 15)
- Policy - Continuing Claim, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 1)
- Policy - Nominal Damage Awards by Referees, 1963-1965 (Box 41, Folder 2)
- Policy - Eligibility Railraod retirement annuity while claim for reinstatement from discharge before NRAB, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 3)
- Lack of Jurisdiction, 1965-1966 (Box 41, Folder 4)
- Policy - Waiving Conference on Property, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 5)
- Policy - Procedure to be followed by Car. settling disputes where no notice given or Ompl. Agreement made (Box 41, Folder 6)
- Policy - Authority of NRAB to Interpret Agreements of Employees in Canada, 1957-1964 (Box 41, Folder 7)
- Referees - Dissatisfaction with General Correspondence, 1962-1969 (Box 41, Folder 8)
- National Railroad Adjustment Board=Supplemental Referees, Days Charged, Cases Handled, 1962-1966 (Box 41, Folder 9)
- NRAB Policy - Extra Men, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 10)
- NRAB - Third Party Issue ARL Notes and Papers, 1966-1970 (Box 41, Folder 11)
- NRAB - Third Party Cases (Lists and Category of Pending Cases), 1967-1968 (Box 41, Folder 12)
- NRAB Policy - Time Limit Rule, 1954-1969 (Box 41, Folder 13)
- NRAB Policy - Third Party, 1954-1971 (Box 41, Folder 14)
- C.L. Dennis Reading File 1969 International Vice President and VPs Reading File, 1971 (Box 42, Folder 1)
- National Movement - General, 1969 (Box 43, Folder 1)
- Assessment Percentages for Various Rules Movements (Box 43, Folder 2)
- History - National Wage and Rules Movements - USA, 1941-1964 (Box 43, Folder 3)
- Mailing Instructions and Distribution: Strike Ballots, National Movements, etc. Marked Directory, 1962-1967 (Box 43, Folder 4)
- System Cooperative Agreement, 1931 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  4/19/1931
- Extra Copies all letters re vacations, 1968 (Box 43, Folder 6)
- Assessments - 1941 Vacation and Wage Movement, 1941-1954 (Box 43, Folder 7)
- Vacation Agreement - Copy, 1941-1954 (Box 43, Folder 8)
- Extra Copies - Schedule of Payments - Vacation Agreement, 1968 (Box 43, Folder 9)
- Movement, 1941-1945 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  Settled by Agreement 2/23/45 Amended Vacation agreement - Section 6 Notice 6/26/44
- Rules Movement - Rest Day Agreement, 1941-1945 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  7/13/1945
- Assessments - Financial Reports 1944 Movement, 1944-1951 (Box 43, Folder 12)
- Rest Day Rule Agreement, 1944-1945 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  7/13/45 - Section 6 Notice 12/15/44 Effective 3/1/45
- Wage Movement - Wage Increase Agreement, 1945-1946 (Box 43, Folder 14)
  5/25/1946
- Assessments - Financial Reports - 1947 Movement, 1947-1948 (Box 43, Folder 15)
- Rules and Wage Movement Agreement, 40 Hour Week Agreement, 1948-1949 (Box 43, Folder 16)
  3/19/1949
- Assessments - Expenses - 1948 Rules and Wage Movement, 1948-1952 (Box 43, Folder 17)
- Extra Copies - all letters on service on rest days, 1968-1969 (Box 43, Folder 18)
- Movement - Gutrie Award, 1952-1953 (Box 43, Folder 19)
  3/18/1953
- Movement - Wage Increase Agreement, 1951-1953 (Box 43, Folder 20)
  3/1/1951
- Union Shop and Check Off, 1952-1965 (Box 43, Folder 21)
  Notice: 2/5/51 Emergency Board #98 - NMB Case A-3744, Strike Notice: 4/2/53 Agreement 8/29/52 Effective 9/22/52
- Assessments - Union Shop Movement, 1958-1967 (Box 43, Folder 22)
- Tennessee, Alabama, and Georgia '51 US Movement, 1969 (Box 43, Folder 23)
- 1953 Rules Movement - General, 1953-1965 (Box 43, Folder 24)
- 1953 Rules Movement - Assessments, 1956-1966 (Box 43, Folder 25)
- L&N Agreement, 1955 (Box 43, Folder 26)
  May 20,1955
- Calendar Time Limits - Article V, 1954-1968 (Box 43, Folder 27)
  8/21/54 Agreement
- 1955 Health and Welfare Movement Emergency Board No. 114 (Box 43, Folder 28)
- Agreement Wage and Health and Welfare Movement, 1955 (Box 43, Folder 29)
  12/21/1955
- L&N Agreement, 1955 (Box 43, Folder 30)
  5/20/1955
- 1955 Health and Welfare and Wage Movement Agreement, Emergency Board 114 Report, 1955-1956 (Box 43, Folder 31)
- Settlement 1959 Rules Movement: Vacation and Holiday, Health, Welfare, and Wage Agreement, 1959-1963 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  August 19,1960
- 1961 Wage and Rules Movement General Agreement, MB Case A-6627 Emergency Board #145, 1961-1963 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  6/5/1962
- Settlement - 1956 Wage Movement, 1956-1961 (Box 44, Folder 3)
- Cost of Living Agreement, 1954-1965 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  December 3,1954
- 1963 Rules Movement - Assessments and Funds, 1964-1969 (Box 44, Folder 5)
- Agreement, Emergency Board Reports 161-162-163, 1963-1965 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  11/20/64 and 2/7/65
- Agreement Settling 1966 Wage and Rules Movement except Article IV, To be settled under ARB #298, 1966-1967 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  Notice 5/10/66 Agreement 1/13/67
- 1966 Wage and Rules Movement - Distribution, 1967 (Box 44, Folder 8)
- 1966 Wage and Rules Movement Assessments-Expenses and Legal Fees (Box 44, Folder 9)
- 1967 Employment Security Movement Agreement, 1967-1968 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  6/24/68 Section 6 Notice 3/15/67 Settled by Agreement 6/24/68
- ARL Notes on 1967 Employment Security Movement (Box 44, Folder 11)
- 1967 Employment Security Movement - Assessments, 1969 (Box 44, Folder 12)
- Method Distribution and Determining Agreement 1967-68 Movement of Classification and Evaluation Fund Article V, 1967-1968 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  June 24,1968
- Vacation-Holiday General Correspondence, 1968 (Box 44, Folder 14)
- Wage, Vacation, and Holiday Movement, 1968 (Box 44, Folder 15)
  (Section 6 Notice 5/29/68) Agreement, June 24,1968 (Article V Classification and Evaluation Fund)
- Wage and Rules Movement - Assessments, 1969 (Box 44, Folder 16)
- Vacation Notice, 1969-1970 (Box 44, Folder 17)
  May 29,1969 - General Correspondence
- Wage and Rules Movement - Canadian, 1970-1971 (Box 44, Folder 18)
- Health and Welfare Program, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 19)
- Article VIII, 1971 (Box 44A, Folder 1)
  2/25/71 Agreement - General Correspondence
- Article VIII, 1971 (Box 44A, Folder 2)
  2/25/71 Agreement
- Article VIII, 1971-1972 (Box 44A, Folder 3)
  2/25/71 Agreement 2
- Article VIII, 1971 (Box 44A, Folder 4)
  2/25/71 Agreement Division 3
- Article VIII, 1971 (Box 44A, Folder 5)
- Article VIII, 1971 (Box 44A, Folder 6)
- Article VIII, 1971 (Box 44A, Folder 7)
  2/25/71 Agreement Division 1
- Article VIII, 1971 (Box 44A, Folder 8)
- Article VIII, 1971 (Box 44A, Folder 9)
- Article VIII, 1971 (Box 44A, Folder 10)
- Article VIII, 1971 (Box 44A, Folder 11)
- Article VIII, 1971 (Box 44A, Folder 12)
- Article VIII, 1972 (Box 44A, Folder 13)
  2/25/71 Agreement Division 15
- Article VIII, 1971 (Box 44A, Folder 14)
- Article VIII, 1972 (Box 44A, Folder 15)
- Article VIII, 1971 (Box 44A, Folder 16)
- Article VIII, 1971 (Box 44A, Folder 17)
- Article VIII, 1971 (Box 44A, Folder 18)
  2/25/71 Agreement Division 25
- Article VIII, 1971 (Box 44A, Folder 19)
  2/25/71 Agreement Division 27
- Article VIII, 1971 (Box 44A, Folder 20)
  2/25/71 Agreement Division 28
- Article VIII, 1969-1971 (Box 44A, Folder 21)
- Article VIII, 1971 (Box 44A, Folder 22)
- Article VIII, 1971 (Box 44A, Folder 23)
- Article VIII, 1971 (Box 44A, Folder 24)
- Article VIII, 1971 (Box 44A, Folder 25)
- Article VIII, 1971 (Box 44A, Folder 26)
- Article VIII, 1971 (Box 44A, Folder 27)
- Article VIII, 1971 (Box 44A, Folder 28)
- Article VIII, 1971 (Box 44A, Folder 29)
  2/25/71 Agreement Division 46
- Article VIII, 1971 (Box 44A, Folder 30)
- Article VIII, 1971 (Box 44A, Folder 31)
  2/25/71 Agreement Division 53
- Article VIII, 1971 (Box 44A, Folder 32)
- Article VIII, 1971 (Box 44A, Folder 33)
- Article VIII, 1971-1972 (Box 44A, Folder 34)
- Article VIII, 1971 (Box 44A, Folder 35)
- Article VIII, 1971 (Box 44A, Folder 36)
- Article VIII, 1971 (Box 44A, Folder 37)
- Article VIII, 1971 (Box 44A, Folder 38)
- Article VIII, 1971 (Box 44A, Folder 39)
- Article VIII, 1971-1972 (Box 44A, Folder 40)
- Article VIII, 1971 (Box 44A, Folder 41)
- Article VIII, 1971 (Box 44A, Folder 42)
- Article VIII, 1971 (Box 44A, Folder 43)
- Article VIII, 1971 (Box 44A, Folder 44)
- Article VIII, 1971 (Box 44A, Folder 45)
- Wage and Rules Movement: Strike Ballot, 1969-1971 (Box 45, Folder 1)
- Wage-Holiday-Accidental Injury or Death Movement -General Correspondence, 1969-1971 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  Section 6 Notice 9/2/69
- Employment Security - Guaranteed Annual Wage Movement - General Correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box 45, Folder 3)
- Hospital, Surgical, Medical and Life Insurance Movement - Carrier's Section 6 Notice, 1969-1970 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  Various Dates
- Hospital, Surgical, Medical and Life Insurance Movement General Correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box 45, Folder 5)
- Canadian Wage and Rules Movement, 1970 (Box 45, Folder 6)
- By-Laws - Atchison, Topeka, and Santa Fe, 1927-1950 (Box 46, Folder 1)
- By-Laws - Atlantic Coast Line Railraod, 1945 (Box 46, Folder 2)
- By-Laws - Chicago and Western Indiana Railroad, 1943 (Box 46, Folder 3)
- By-Laws - Baltimore and Ohio Railroad, 1945-1949 (Box 46, Folder 4)
- By-Laws - Boston and Albany Railroad, 1949 (Box 46, Folder 5)
- By-Laws - Boston Elevated (Box 46, Folder 6)
- By-Laws - Boston and Maine, 1950-1951 (Box 46, Folder 7)
- By-Laws - Canadian Pacific Railway Company, 1942-1952 (Box 46, Folder 8)
- By-Laws - Canadian National, 1946-1953 (Box 46, Folder 9)
- By-Laws - Central Railroad of New Jersey (Box 46, Folder 10)
- By-Laws - Chesapeake and Ohio Railroad, 1927-1949 (Box 46, Folder 11)
- By-Laws - Chicago, Burlington, and Quincy Railraod, 1939-1953 (Box 46, Folder 12)
- By-Laws - Chicago and Eastern Illinois Railroad (Box 46, Folder 13)
- By-Laws - Chicago, St. Paul, Minneapolis and Omaha Railway, 1941-1955 (Box 46, Folder 14)
- By-Laws - Chicago, Rock Island and Pacific Railway, 1942-1952 (Box 46, Folder 15)
- By-Laws - Chicago and Northwestern Railway, 1946-1951 (Box 46, Folder 16)
- By-Laws - Kentucky and Indiana Terminal Railroad (Box 46, Folder 17)
- By-Laws - Delaware, Kackawanna, Western Railroad Company, 1944-1947 (Box 46, Folder 18)
- By-Laws - Denver and Rio Grande Western Railroad, 1936-1952 (Box 46, Folder 19)
- By-Laws - Erie Railroad, 1949-1952 (Box 46, Folder 20)
- By-Laws - Hudson and Manhattan Railroad Company, 1939-1952 (Box 46, Folder 21)
- By-Laws - Lehigh Valley Railraod, 1919-1948 (Box 46, Folder 22)
- By-Laws - Long Island Railraod Company, 1947-1952 (Box 46, Folder 23)
- By-Laws - Louisville and Nashville Railroad Company, 1936-1947 (Box 46, Folder 24)